https://www.amberlotus.com/permissions-privacy-policy/

My Account
Enjoy FREE shipping on domestic orders of $50 or more!Order by 12/16 to receive for Christmas.
Loading... Please wait...
Your Account | Wish Lists
| Your Basket
Search
Calendars
Featured CalendarsWall CalendarsDesk Pad CalendarsHardcover Deluxe PlannersOn-The-Go Weekly PlannersPoster Art Wall CalendarsMini Wall CalendarsEngagement CalendarsPlanner StickersKatie Daisy CollectionGeninne Zlatkis CollectionPAPAYA & FIREWEED Collection
Greeting Cards
New ReleasesOccasionArtist SeriesHoliday Boxed Sets
Coloring Books
Journals
Books
Featured
Blog
Artist SpotlightHoliday LoreFree Downloadables
Featured | Amber Lotus Publishing
Eco-Initiatives
Environmental StatementOne Million Trees PlantedArt, Commerce, and Service
HomePermissions & Privacy Policy
Permissions & Privacy Policy
Permissions
All materials published by Amber Lotus Publishing are protected by domestic and international copyright laws. You are legally required to obtain permission prior to the reproduction or redistribution of any of our materials.
Amber Lotus Publishing has obtained permission to use the images and text featured in our products from our partner artists, authors, photographers, and publishing companies. We do not have the right to grant permission for reuse of the images or text by others. Please contact the appropriate partner for copyright permissions. Please be respectful of our artists and understand that if you copy their work without permission you are infringing on their ability to make a living.
Privacy Policy
Protecting your privacy is important to us. Amber Lotus Publishing will never sell, rent, or share your personal information (including but not limited to your name, email address, physical address, and phone number). Any information shared with us will be used in service of processing your order or providing a seamless shopping experience.
Information We Collect and How We Use It
In processing your order, we may require various forms of personal information from you, depending on the payment method you choose. We will never ask for more information than is necessary for the bank to verify your payment. If we have trouble processing your order, the contact information you provided is used to get in touch with you. We do not share that information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order.
IP addresses are recorded for security purposes only during the checkout process.
On some pages, you can submit feedback or leave comments; we may ask you for some additional information so we can better address an issue, but you are never required to leave additional information. The only times you will get email from us are during the purchasing process, if you ask a question, or subscribe to our newsletter.
We use non-identifying and computer-generated information for statistical purposes only. This includes, among other things, domain, country, browser, platform, and pages visited. Most websites routinely do this, and we never share any of this information with anyone who is not directly involved with the maintenance of our website.
Cookies
This website uses cookies. A cookie is a piece of data containing information about a user; that data is stored on the user’s hard drive. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.
Our Commitment to Data Security
We proudly take every precaution to protect our customers’ privacy and security. When the checkout process asks you to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and CCV), that information is protected with SSL encryption software. While on a secure page (such as the checkout screens), the padlock icon on web browsers such as Firefox or Microsoft Internet Explorer appears locked, instead of unlocked/open as during normal internet use. All of our customers’ data is restricted within our offices; only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our financial manager or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers that store sensitive material are kept in a secure, locked environment.
If you have any questions or concerns about the security of our website or our privacy policies, you are always welcome to send us an email.
Updated May 25, 2018
WE PLANT TREES to offset our carbon footprint and resource usage — ONE MILLION and growing!
Amber Lotus Info
Environmental Statement
The Amber Lotus Story
Artist Submissions
Permissions & Privacy Policy
Customer Service
Wholesale
View Our 2021 Catalog
Shipping & Returns
Contact Us | 800.326.2375
Amber Lotus Publishing offers earth-friendly calendars, greeting cards, journals, and coloring books featuring a diverse collection of artists and authors such as Katie Daisy, Geninne D Zlatkis, Alex Grey, Meera Lee Patel, Thich Nhat Hanh, Pema Chödrön, Eckhart Tolle, Louise Hay, Ram Dass, and more!
Copyright © 2020 Amber Lotus Publishing. All rights are reserved.
Copying of images or text is not permitted without written consent from Amber Lotus Publishing.
Please be respectful of our artists and understand that if you copy their work without permission you are infringing on their ability to make a living.
All prices are in USD
